Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every
wall that's in our wake!
Go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world
believing that surely someday.
We just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up. Way up high.
Always step up.
If waves erupt up to the sky.
Never give up. Our wishes.
They will come together.
And lead us on.
For the future.
We drift on.
Riding the waves.
Towards another shore.
Day by day.
There are many meetings.
Many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag. We fly.
I'll remember.
The pain within, I'll keep
it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly,
but I won't surrender.
This freedom, I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up, raise up
the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up, we'll get past
everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up way up high.
Always step up, if waves are
rough, jump through the sky.
Never give up, our wishes
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
Listen up, you pirate scum!
The tanker is your territory
and you better stay on it!
This line here is the division
between good and evil.
So don't you even dare
think of crossing over.
Them's the rules to live by, Straw Hats.
Where the hell did you get an
idea to waste your time with this?
Huh?
The only thing I told you to do was
not fraternize with the pirates.
And there's no better way to enforce that.
Men will respect the line.
We done determined that the line
don't applicate to the medics, though.
I got into contact with the G5 base.
We're gonna wait right here
for them to pick us up. Sir!
What? That's nuts!
Don't turn yourself in, Brownbeard!
Seems like a waste since you
and my crew are friends now.
Ha-ha-ha!
Turns out Caesar was exposing his men to
small amounts of poison this whole time.
But they said the government will
treat us if we hand ourselves over.
Okay, fair enough.
Hey, what the hell, Straw Hat?
I just told you not to
step across the damn line!
Clean out your filthy ears!
Why should I care?
That's your stupid rule, not mine.
Anyway, I figure I would rather rot in
prison than die of Caesar's guinea pig.
But, kid, I can't tell you how good
it felt to watch you clock Caesar.
Thank you, Luffy.
One, two, three!
Come on, go with all your might!
I really wish somebody told me we
were going to be using this tanker.
I knew we were going to have to fix it.
Well, I would have found
another place to brawl it out.
Huh?
What's with the screaming?
Chop, are you okay?
Help me! Huh?
You've got to stop him, hurry!
So, what?
He's committing murder!
What?
Who's the murderer?
Who the heck are you talking about?
Law is killing them!
Really, Traffy?
And why is Brooke freaking out?
I also committed a murder.
I mean, Keenumon was already dead, but...
I shattered his body!
He's dead and you shattered him?
You killed him again?
I don't want you to fix him.
What do you mean, fix him?
He was already dead before you broke him.
What if we glue him back together?
How are you two not
getting that he's dead?
You're supposed to be dead!
Why are you attacking him, Sanji?
Why wouldn't I?
We were just discussing how
he's dead, and now he's not.
You should be happy about
it, not kicking him.
It was a reflex. Jeez, sorry.
Well, it is a surprise.
Are you guys seeing this?
The guy who they thought
was killed is really alive?
Oh, I'm so utterly relieved, Kin'emon.
I thought you were gone for good. Father!
Momonosuke!
Father!
I feared that I would never see you again.
And I thought you were dead.
Huh?
That kid's Momo?
Oh yeah, he said something
about being a human once.
Huh?
He is not normally this naked, though.
And poof!
This kimono suits you quite splendidly.
Just like a true son of Wado.
Tell me, father.
How did you know that I...
was...
Momonosuke!
Get out here now!
You sicko!
How could you do that to those poor kids?
I saw what you were doing
and you are gonna regret it!
There's a reason I told
you not to look inside.
I had a feeling you wouldn't understand.
Why I would slice them up.
Oh, there's drugs.
This was the fastest way to get
that poison out of their systems.
Look, the raccoon's here! Hey, Mr.
Raccoon Wait, you guys are all okay?
The guy with the big puffy
hat just came to see us.
He cut the bad drugs out of our bodies.
It was crazy.
I was real scared at first,
but I feel awesome now.
He chopped us up into little
pieces and it was real funny.
I'm hungry now.
He was helping them.
I'm kind of worried, though,
because Mocha still hasn't woken up.
She was fighting to try to
save all of us, wasn't she?
The master was always so nice.
I had no idea he was such a bad guy.
My memory's fuzzy, but I remember when
Mocha coughed her blood and passed out.
Hey, Mr.
Raccoon, I'm actually a reindeer.
Mocha, she'll be okay, right?
Can she still go home with us?
Please say yes.
Of course she can.
You're safe now.
The nightmare's finally over.
Where's the lady with the orange hair?
Yeah, she promised that she was
going to help us all get home.
And after everything she's done for
us, we wanted to tell her thanks.
Hey, kids?
Let's get you all home.
The Navy's going to take you back
to your parents, safe and sound.
But we don't want to go with the Navy!
What about the robot?
And the stretchy guy?
Or the guy with weird eyebrows?
Mmm, smells good. What?
I wonder what Sanji's cooking up for us.
I'm starving.
There we go.
That's looking pretty straight to me.
Just needs a super quick fix
and it'll be good to go. Nami?
Did you manage to sort out
a deal with the Marines?
Yep.
I'm going to leave the
children in their hands.
I talked to Big Game about saving them,
but I kind of doubt their parents would
be too keen on pirates bringing them home.
Yeah, you got a point.
I think we've dealt with enough wrongful
accusations of kidnapping in our lives.
Might as well just let the
good guys take all the credit.
Like always.
Besides.
I have a bad history with most Marines,
but if they're women,
it's a different story.
Yeah? Why's that?
Well, they make me feel safe
Oh yeah, your mom was in the Navy, right?
Don't know how I forgot that
She was, but that's beside the point.
You can always count on
a strong female soldier.
Ain't that the truth.
It sounds gross when you say it.
I was just agreeing.
New Kama Kimpo technique.
99 fundamental recipes.
A cold, exhausted body needs a healthy
heaping helping of fat and warmth.
So I made hormone soup du
Giri with sea pig pork.
I know you've been running on
an empty stomach for days now.
So start with the soup and eat it slowly.
I want it now!
I bet you're starving, aren't you?
You're so lucky, Sanji's the best cook.
I do not want this!
You cannot force me to
eat your strange food!
Hold it right there, punk.
The hell are you doing with that bowl?
I don't care if you're a kid.
Anyone wastes food around me?
Well, then I waste them.
I gladly accept your fee. What?
Uh, hey. Delicious! What is this?
My streak is returning.
These delicacies you've prepared
are shockingly delectable.
My father!
Their food is fine to eat, son.
Accept their kindness.
My life was saved on this island,
and they were the ones who saved it—it was
a gift to have met such
trustworthy people!
All this time, you haven't had
a single bite to eat, have you?
Such a strong boy!
It must have been awful!
You have nothing to worry about anymore.
We must have faith that everyone
else is alive and well now.
Let us choose to live!
You hear me, momonosuke!
It's
that good!
It's tasty enough to cry! Moron!
They've clearly gone through some crap!
What the hell happened
to those two? Hello!
What happened to your sacred
boundary between good and evil?
You jerks!
We're calling for a ceasefire!
Well, if that's the case—that's
the booth from the tanker!
We're on it!
We need to talk, Straw Hat!
There's no time to stick around and eat!
They're gonna be right on our tail!
We've got to.
got to leave now.
That bat huh?
Tell your crew we've got a ship out.
Alright I'll let
him know.
Listen up guys.
See you again and get down.
Cheers.
Is something wrong?
But father the true warriors shouldn't
allow themselves to weep in front of others.
In moments!
What are you doing, little baby?
Here's to you, my brother. Yeah!
Watch very closely now.
Oh, thank you.
Lock!
Vice Admiral Smokey!
We're taking a team back to Caesar's lab!
What happened?
We forced Caesar to tell
us the gas is weakness!
All our guys are still alive!
We're heading back to rescue him!
What the?
How is Smoker still alive?
Frankly, although I made you a promise,
you can't possibly expect me to keep it.
You're a pirate.
But if you wanted to silence me, you had
plenty of opportunities to do it earlier.
Using Straw Hat, what
exactly are you planning?
Using him—what makes you
think he's not using me?
Well,
there's four of them
right, so which one is it?
If you really need to know, I'm talking
about kaido king of the beasts—sure,
as long as shanks isn't
first, I'm cool with that!
with that
And besides, I'm already planning on
crushing all four emperors anyway.
You seriously think you can beat them all?
We share a common goal, but
I warn you, it ain't easy.
These are the strongest
fighters in the seas.
They've gone head-to-head with Whitebeard
and lived to tell about it, remember?
Not only that,
our target Kaido is considered the
most powerful creature in the world.
What? Creature?
He's not even human?
We'll work together to beat Kaido.
After that, our alliance comes to an end.
If you're curious about our
chances of success, well,
they're exceptionally low,
and I'll leave it at that.
You gotta be kidding me?
It's not a plan—it's a suicide mission!
Luffy, in that case.
My
answer is yes.
What can we talk this
over for, just a minute?
Not
that I wanted you alive—that's
just how it worked out.
Don't read into it, by the way.
After we leave here, I'm thinking about
heading over to Green Bits. Who knows?
The Straw Hats may be useful, or maybe
I'm the one who's useful to them.
to them
You know, for Marines,
you guys aren't half bad.
I know you're pirate scum, but
hell, I'd let you buy me a drink.
I thought you guys
decided to use the tanker.
That was a plan, but you see,
Nami and Chopper are both
saying we can't leave just yet.
At least not until we
make sure the kids are
sailing away from Punk
Hazard safe and sound.
That, and we don't want to sit around
and wait for more marines to show up.
You have the ship.
You gotta take the kids and all.
All right, little tikes, on the double!
Who is ready to go home?
There's plenty of room.
Since this tanker belongs to
us now, here's the border.
Don't even think about
crossing over to our side.
This is the division
between good and evil.
Keep back, not one more
step. What, this again?
But we were all just partying
together a minute ago.
What's your point?
The party's over.
Not like we don't appreciate what you did.
We are grateful for the meal.
Still, pirates are our sworn enemy.
We're scumming the world.
Raise the sales!
Huh?
Hey, what gives?
Miss Naomi!
Can you hear me, Chopper?
Where's the robot? Don't know.
I can't see the pirates
with that thing in the way.
They're trying to block their view?
Give me a break.
It's a barrier!
Protecting the children from seeing you!
I thought we worked out
our issues here, G5!
Aren't we bros? Oh well.
At least they're safely aboard.
We stand for justice! Cheer for us!
Don't let these pirates
try to fool you, kids!
They're bad guys!
Pirates are only scum!
Dregs of society!
But Marines stand for Law
and Order! Hurry! Hurry up!
It's the poisonous gas
from outside! Oh, no!
Better start running if you want to live!
Tashigi mentioned she's
going to reach out to
Vegapunk for assistance
finding a cure for the kids.
Oh, yeah? That's great!
Let us see now!
Get out of the way, you jerk!
If any of you want to say goodbye to
the pirates, you're just rotten kids!
And if you want to thank them,
we'll drag you off the tanker
and leave you on the island.
Pirates are good-for-nothing punks.
Marines are where it's at.
But when we asked them for their help,
they gave up without a second thought.
They didn't even know who
we were, what was wrong.
But they took us with them and
never complained about our size.
We were slowing them down When can
we leave this place and go home?
Trust me, it'll happen soon.
Just hang tight.
We were trapped on this island.
And no one was going to come see us.
But the pirates did.
I'm sorry.
So sorry.
That we didn't get here
sooner to save you from him.
Pirates are filthy.
Everyone knows they don't take baths.
On the other hand, the Navy.
Why are they doing this?
They won't let us say thank you!
The Navy's worse than seasoners!
Don't say that! I'm sorry!
We are pirates, and the Navy is great!
Pirates are cowards!
The Navy is brave!
We're brave and noble
and righteous! Stop it!
This instant!
Shame on you all!
You, you don't get into shaking!
We have to keep saying
bad things about him,
or else we might we might
do the unforgivable!
We might end up liking these guys,
even if they are pirates.
Bunch of weirdos!
Bye, pirate guys and gals!
We'll miss you.
Thank you so much for saving all of us.
When we grow up, you know what
we want to be: Pirates like you!
Please don't!
Well, it's time for us to head out to you.
Hey, why's this one tagging along with us?
Oh, I guess we forgot to tell
you about the alliance we made.
Hey, Straw Hat!
Next time we see you, you
won't get off so easy!
You better be ready for us!
OK!
We'll lock you up and throw away the key!
I wouldn't be surprised if the Straw
Hats made a deal with the devil.
Lucky bastards.
If the weather was cloudy, I could have
taken my sky path straight to them.
Young Master!
You won't believe this!
It was law!
That traitor was in with the Straw Hats!
And we let it happen!
I wish I was dead!
You needed me, and now I'm just a burden!
I'm sorry!
I failed you!
This is the life yacht that
was on our tanker, right?
I'm almost too ashamed to
say, but after I hung up...
No need.
I can fill in the blanks.
All you did was follow
the orders I gave you.
Well, color me surprised.
It's the boss.
I didn't expect you to show up in person.
Hello, Law.
It's been far too long.
A real shame you didn't
choose to show your face.
I figure you want to know where Caesar is.
He's safely in our hands.
Joker, where the hell
are you? They got me.
Help me, please.
Question regarding the state of my
cohort's bodies. Where are they?
I couldn't say, nor does it
particularly interest me.
Let's negotiate.
come on lock get serious
here stop pretending
you're an adult and let's cut to the chase
tell me where are you
right now answer quicker
I may get mad oh you'll
get mad and what about
your business partner
what's his name I keep
forgetting that's right
Kaido King of the beasts
and one of the four
emperors now i'm just a brat
but if there's anyone
you'd want to keep from
getting angry i think it'd be him i wonder
how he might react after
he finds out you can't
produce smile who knows
but he doesn't strike me
as the bargaining type i
imagine a fierce battle
would ensue master your
turn of blue when it's
over you'll be gone all
right you've carried the
joke far enough so let's
discuss the terms like
grown-ups what do you
want to trade for caesar
resign from the seven warlords that's
all can you believe the nerve of
this punk if joker quits he'll be
forced to leave dress rosa come now
i'm only asking for you to abandon
a decade of hard work to go back to
being a simple pirate unfortunately
once that happens the navy admirals at
headquarters won't be able to turn
a blind eye to you any longer you
have until tomorrow if I look in
the morning paper and see a headline
announcing your resignation from the
warlords then I will call you and the
deal is on but if I don't see it then
my offer is as good as dead so long
Just a damn minute! Law!
Young Master!
I'm gonna kill that brat.